Hi, I really hope you enjoy the course, and in this video I want to show you how you
can leave a review.
Please click on my learning page, find the course and click leave a review here.
You can choose how many stars you want to leave to the course, and provide a feedback
or some comments you want to share with alter all other students.
And click save and continue.
On this page you can also check some options, how was this course, I'll check yes, I like
this course.
And after you choose options you'll see is reasonable for this course you can click save
and continue.
Also, if you want you can share this feedback on your social media, just click share.
You can co-op easily in code, choose an existing social media, and then click save
and exit.
Also, if you want to edit your review you can click here on your rating and you will see
text edit rating and then click edit and do the same steps as you did before.